来从我手中窃取提名了吗 就像她窃取南卡罗来纳时那样?
to steal the nomination from me like she stole South Carolina?
美国独立战争由从英国手中夺取南卡罗来纳州开始
窃取南卡罗莱纳本来就是
Stealing South Carolina is the bedrock
我们政治体系的根基好吗
of our political system, Senator.
好吧 这就是梅耶对待犯罪计划的随意态度
Well, there it is, that casual Meyer attitude
和她丈夫一样
towards criminal enterprise, just like her husband.
- 前夫 -继夫
- Ex-husband. - Step-husband.
如果你想不出来怎么窃取南卡罗来纳
If you can't figure out how to steal South Carolina,
你就不配当总统
you have no business being president.
- 噢 这是你的想法吗? - 是的 我没错对吧?
- Oh, is that how you feel? - Yes! Am I right?
嘿! 好了!
Hey! Hey! All right!
现在 每个周日评论员和政治学专业学生
Right now, every Sunday pundit and poli-sci major
第一次投票未确定提名人选时,候选人需要召开协调会议进行商议
都把这个协调会议
is treating this brokered convention
看作是个有着大胸的大学体操运动员
like it's a big-titted college gymnast